http://www.centurydocumentimaging.com/privacy-policy.asp

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form. When filling out a form, you may be asked to
enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the
information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer
service requests and support needs)
To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than
for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you
information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news,
updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe
from receiving future emails, reply to Sales@CenturyDocumentImaging.com with your request.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal identifiable information.
This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our
business, or servcing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may
also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our
site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, nonpersonal identifiable
visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.
These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no
responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to
protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to
information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last
modified on 10-25-2010.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Century Document Imaginginfo@CenturyDocumentImaging.com1.800.356.3456
Need More Information?
If you need pricing or more information, send us your request below and a Century representative will promptly get you the information you're looking for.
Name
Email
Phone
Comments
Send
Protected by reCAPTCHA. Privacy - Terms
Nationwide: (800) 356-3456
Houston: (713) 221-1990
